NIKOLA PETROVSKI

FRONTEND WEB DEVELOPER



077 666 775



petrovskinikolag@gmail.com



Nikola Rusinski 5-A, 7000 Bitola



www.nikolagp.com



PROFILE

I am a self-taught ambitious web developer with three years of experience in web design and development with WordPress CMS. More than one year dedicated to learn the programming logic and algorithms with JavaScript. Prefer VueJS but open to learn new technologies. Strong creative and analytical skills. Team player with an eye for detail.

SKILLS

- Front End Coding
- Problem-Solving
- CMS Development
- Computer Literacy
- · Web Design
- Design Thinking
- Strong Communication
- Project Management
- Project Management Tools

EDUCATION

SELF-TAUGHT: JS, VUEJS

Udemy, Youtube, freeCodeCamp

2021 - present

MERN: JAVASCRIPT & NODE.JS

& MONGODB

Semos, Skopje

02-04.2020

WORDPRESS COURSE

Brainster, Skopje

08.2018

MA IN INTERNATIONAL LAW

Law Faculty, University St. Kliment Ohridski, Bitola

2012 - 2015

BAIN LAW

Law Faculty, University St. Kliment Ohridski, Bitola

2008 - 2012

EXPERIENCE

WEB ADMINISTRATOR

Free Cities Foundation (remote) www.free-cities.org

06.2022 - Present

- Website design/development for projects and conferences
- Adding new features and maintaining the existing websites

LEAD WORDPRESS FORMATTER

Recurrent / Brookline Media (remote) www.recurrent.io

10.2019-10.2022

- Preparing training videos and guides for new formatters and improving the training process
- Communication with the Executive/Deputy Editor
- Managing the team of formatters
- Suggesting ideas for improving the work in general

FREELANCE WORDPRESS DEVELOPER

Upwork, Jobrack, Social Media Channels

01.2020 - Present

• Design and development of websites in WordPress CMS

PROJECT COORDINATOR

European Cultural Epicentar www.eke.mk

Libertania CCP - Bitola www.libertania.org

11.2019 - 01.2020

Writing and managing projects

COORDINATOR OF MEMBERSHIP AND COMMUNICATION

National Youth Council of Macedonia, Skopje

www.nms.org.mk

02.2017 - 11.2019

- Responsible for new members and verification of membership
- Enlarging the network and recruiting new member-organizations